myfootinthedoor.com 2016-06-20

# Privacy Policy

|  |  Privacy Policy   
---  
This privacy policy sets out how we use and protect any information that you give My Foot In The Door (“MFITD”) when you use this Web site www.myfootinthedoor.com. We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this Web site, you can be assured that it will be only used in accordance with this privacy statement.   
What we collect :   
  
  * Registration 
    * Name, email address, password and university 
    * billing information such as credit card number, expiration date, and billing address
    * demographic information such as postcode, preference and interests
    * Names and email address of third parties
  * Profile Information

Once you have created an account with us you are then able to disclose more information about yourself such as your career choice, education, experience, internships, if you were in the military. This information is used to build a biography on you so that other users are able to see what accomplishments you have reached. Completing your biography questions plays a crucial roll in transforming the hiring process. It allows candidates to finder better fitting jobs more efficiently.   
The additional information we ask for is how many siblings you have, if you are the oldest, and other demographic information such as if you were part of a varsity sports team or if you volunteered for certain organizations.   
You have the option to store your billing information, if you wish to do so we will store this information on an encrypted page. No one has access to this information but you. We will not use this information for any purpose other than to bill you for services. You may also at any time view your transactions, amount, subscription, and status by logging in and selecting “billing details” from the name tab located at the top right hand side of your account.   
You have the ability to upload a photo to your account, please be aware that if you wish to do so this may be viewable by other users of the site. You may remove your photo at anytime by selecting “account settings” and “change picture”.   
Use of Your Information   
  
  * We use this information to create an account for you, allow you to interact with other users of the site, submit your resume for review, bill you for services, and send you newsletters as well as other promotional emails that may be of interest to you. We use third party information to invite them to visit the site, to send recommendation request and receive recommendations. 
  * The information you provide to MFITD will give others the ability to identify your education, gender, ethnic background, age, and other personal information about you. By providing information for your registration, personal profile and answering your biography questions, you are agreeing to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy and MFITD terms of use that allows MFITD to process information about you. 

Resume   
We provide you the ability to import your resume and a cover letter so that you have it saved on the site for future uses. You may at any time delete the resume from our site by logging into your account and selecting delete. Other users of the site, that have permission to see your profile, have the ability to evaluate your resume. You may choose for a network community or large community to be able to evaluate your resume. Peer Resume evaluation allows your peers to evaluate your profile with your consent. Your name , address and any other personal information will not be shown to the third party for any reason. Regarding recruiters, employers and Universities, you have the ability to set your resume to be public or private.   
Inbox Messages/Audio and Video Chat   
You have the ability to send private messages, chat via audio and/or video to other users of the site as well as companies in which you have expressed interest. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas, including your name and email address, may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. Your personal email address and contact information will not be shared with other users unless both parties indicate that they would like to communicate with each other. To request removal of your personal information from these areas of the site, contact us at [privacy@myfootinthedoor.com](mailto:privacy@myfootinthedoor.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.   
Connections   
You have the ability to connect with other users of the site and invite friends to the site, we will send your friend a one-time email allowing them to visit the site. This information is used only to will help MFITD expand your network. We do not store this information and will not use it for any other purpose. You may control your connections by logging into your account and selecting “connections”.   
Access to Personal Information   
If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete inaccuracies, or deactivate your account by making the change within the settings or billing tab under your name once you have logged in or by emailing us at [ privacy@myfootinthedoor.com](mailto:privacy@myfootinthedoor.com). We will respond to your access request within 30 days.   
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [privacy@myfootinthedoor.com](mailto:privacy@myfootinthedoor.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.   
Privacy Settings   
There are numerous pieces of information like your career choice and education that make up your MFITD profile. What information and with whom you want to share is up to you. You have the ability to set the privacy setting separately for each individual item. For other users, the information can be set as private, public or that it can be viewed only by users that are in your network. As far as employers, recruiters and universities, each item can be set as private or public.   
Security   
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.   
When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).   
Sharing of your Personal Information   
We will not share, sell, rent or trade your personal information with third parties other than as disclosed within this privacy policy.   
We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as processing your payment or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.   
We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.   
If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, you will be notified via email and/or prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or users of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.   
Cookies   
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.   
We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time.   
We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.   
Third Party Cookies   
The use of cookies by third parties is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies.   
Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)   
We employ or our third party advertising partner employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.   
Facebook Connect or other OpenID provider   
You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.   
Import Contacts   
You can import contacts from your Outlook or other email account address book to invite them to become members of our site. We collect the username and password for the email account you wish to import your contacts from and will only use it for that purpose.   
Communications from the Site   
Based upon the personal information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.   
From time to time we may send you promotional, special offers, or newsletters. If you no longer wish to receive these types of communications please opt-out by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each communication.   
Changes in this Privacy Policy   
We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.   
Contact us:   
My Foot In The Door, Inc. 12040 96th Ave NE Suite 127 Kirkland, WA 98034   
|   
---  

MFITD been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](https://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [privacy@myfootinthedoor.com](mailto:privacy@myfootinthedoor.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).
